Kevin Tieu

Sacramento CA, 95823 916-216-1072 | <u>kt216@humboldt.edu</u> GitHub: <u>https://github.com/KevinTieu9</u>

PROFILE

IT Help Desk Technician with 2+ years of experience providing technical assistance and support related to computer systems, hardware, and software. A trusted team member who responds to queries, runs diagnostic programs, isolates problem, and determines and implements the best solution for clients.

EDUCATION AND TECHNICAL SKILLS

Computing Talent Initiative Accelerate Program 2022-Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Expected Fall 2024

Cal Poly Humboldt

Bachelor of Arts in Government 2010-2014

California State University, Sacramento Pi Sigma Alpha Honor Society

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python * CSS * HTML * Javascript * PHP * C++ * SQL

Data Acquisition: Data-mining/Web Scraping

Specific Technologies: React NextJS, PostgreSQL, Prisma ORM, SAS

EXPERIENCE

FreeCodeCamp Classroom App Contributor Oct 2022-Nov 2022 FreeCodeCamp Online

- Collaborated with a team of 2 other interns and a mentor from Uber.
- Contributed to the FreeCodeCamp Classroom App, a project with 1M+ users that aims to help teachers manage student grades at FreeCodeCamp.
- Front-end of the app is built with React using the NextJS framework. The app data is saved to a PostgreSQL database using the Prisma ORM.
- Improved the notification messages to be more user-friendly by introducing the Toastify component and replacing the older vanilla CSS implementation.

ITS Student Assistant 2022-present Cal Poly Humboldt Arcata, CA

- Serve as tier 1 support providing technical assistance via phone, email, or in person to users on the delivery, configuration, set up, maintenance, and troubleshooting of computer systems, hardware, accessories, and software
- Perform quality assurance checks and follow up with customers on all issue resolutions performed
- Provide clear and timely communication to IT department employees and customers
- Stage equipment and resources as required by Support IT projects